Rubin "Hurricane" Carter Papers MS226
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1950 -- 2012; MS226.008; 10.8 Linear Feet
  - Beacon Communications, 1995 -- 2003; MS226.008.008.00001 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Biographies - Rubin, 2007; MS226.008.008.00002 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - BMO Insurance sent February 11, 2012, 2010 -- 2012; MS226.008.008.00003 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Boppre, Jeff - Free the Innocent, 2004; MS226.008.008.00004 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Boxing ephemera, 2000 -- 2001; MS226.008.008.00005 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Brain Dead Speech, 2002; MS226.008.008.00006 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Bright, Stephen, 1994 -- 2001; MS226.008.008.00007 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Brother's Keeper Men's Network International, 2005; MS226.008.008.00008 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Burke's Restoration, 2004 -- 2005; MS226.008.008.00009 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Calgary Jewish Center, 1999; MS226.008.008.00010 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Campaign to End the Death Penalty, 1999 -- 2000; MS226.008.008.00011 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Cardoza, Joshua, 2006; MS226.008.008.00012 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Carter, Mae T (1 of 5), 2000 -- 2002; MS226.008.008.00013 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Carter, Mae T (2 of 5), 2000 -- 2002; MS226.008.008.00014 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Carter, Mae T (3 of 5), 2000 -- 2002; MS226.008.008.00015 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Carter, Mae T (4 of 5), 2000 -- 2002; MS226.008.008.00016 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Carter, Mae T (5 of 5), 2000 -- 2002; MS226.008.008.00017 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Carter, Maurice (1 of 2), 2000 -- 2004; MS226.008.008.00018 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Carter, Maurice (2 of 2), 2000 -- 2004; MS226.008.008.00019 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Chapman, Gwyn, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.008.008.00020 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Chicago Convention, 1998; MS226.008.008.00021 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Citizen's United for the Rehabilitation of Errants (CUBE), 2000; MS226.008.008.00022 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Communities Against Bullying Behavior, 2000; MS226.008.008.00023 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Contracts -The One-Eyed Man, The 16th Round, 2009 -- 2010; MS226.008.008.00024 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Cooper, Kevin - Death Row, San Quentin, California, 2004; MS226.008.008.00025 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Crawford, Steven - freed on bail, Harrisburg, Penn., 2002; MS226.008.008.00026 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Crawford, Steven - press conference, 2002; MS226.008.008.00027 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Cruz, Rolando, 1992 -- 1996; MS226.008.008.00028 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Dalton, Ron, 2009; MS226.008.008.00029 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Death Penalty, 2006 -- 2008; MS226.008.008.00030 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Death Penalty info, 1994 -- 2000; MS226.008.008.00031 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Death - what is it?, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.008.008.00032 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Direct Energy renewal, 2003; MS226.008.008.00033 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Doctorate degree letters, 2003; MS226.008.008.00034 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Driskell, James, 2003; MS226.008.008.00035 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Duplessis orphans, 1999; MS226.008.008.00036 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - Einhorn, Lois - How to forgive yourself and how to forgive others, 2002; MS226.008.008.00037 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - ESPN interview request, 2001; MS226.008.008.00038 (Box data_value_missing_d37076278a65a68b627f92b3b37669f8, Box 8)
  - FBI files - incomplete, 1977 -- 1985; MS226.008.009.00001 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - George Ferguson re: police review, and speeches, 2002 -- 2003; MS226.008.009.00002 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Folkes, Beverly, 2002; MS226.008.009.00003 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Fortress Security group, 2008; MS226.008.009.00004 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Freedman, Jonathan - article drafts, 2003 -- 2004; MS226.008.009.00005 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Friends of Griffith University in the USA, 2008; MS226.008.009.00006 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Future engagements?, 2004; MS226.008.009.00007 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Gee, Errol, 1998; MS226.008.009.00008 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Global Institute for Transformation, 2006; MS226.008.009.00009 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Green, Mel, 2006; MS226.008.009.00010 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Greene, Cy, 2004; MS226.008.009.00011 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Griffith University dinner, 2004; MS226.008.009.00012 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Griffith University honorary doctorate, York University honorary doctorate, 2003; MS226.008.009.00013 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Griffith University Innocence Project, 2009; MS226.008.009.00014 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Gurdjieff, 1999; MS226.008.009.00015 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Halifax-AMJ Campbell van lines, 1999; MS226.008.009.00016 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Hamilton Partnership for Paterson, 2010; MS226.008.009.00017 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Harry Jerome awards, 1996 -- 2001; MS226.008.009.00018 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Hartman, Gerald, 2004; MS226.008.009.00019 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Harvard Law School criminal law series, 2004; MS226.008.009.00020 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Harvard Law School: Race and the Death Penalty conference, 2006; MS226.008.009.00021 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Hirsch, James - manuscript, correspondence, memos, 1995 -- 2000; MS226.008.009.00022 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - History of AIDWYC and introductions, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.008.009.00023 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Hohenberger, Robert, 2000 -- 2006; MS226.008.009.00024 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Hurricane Fund, 1975; MS226.008.009.00025 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Hurricane Fund, 1976; MS226.008.009.00026 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Hynes, Charles J. re: David McCallum, 2006; MS226.008.009.00027 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - The Innocents television series, 2004; MS226.008.009.00028 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - International Boxing Hall of Fame, 2001; MS226.008.009.00029 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Japan - Iweo Hakamada and Todd McKay (1 of 2), 2007 -- 2009; MS226.008.009.00030 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Japan - Iweo Hakamada and Todd McKay (2 of 2), 2003 -- 2009; MS226.008.009.00031 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - JCC Sports Dinner, 1998 -- 1999; MS226.008.009.00032 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Justice issues, 2000; MS226.008.009.00033 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Juvenile court, 2000; MS226.008.009.00034 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Kalish, John, 1999; MS226.008.009.00035 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Kase, John - re: Allen Walker, contracts, 2002 -- 2004; MS226.008.009.00036 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 9)
  - Kelley, Carolyn (1 of 2), 2000 -- 2003; MS226.008.010.00001 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Kelley, Carolyn (2 of 2), 2000 -- 2003; MS226.008.010.00002 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Kelley, Carolyn (1 of 3), 2002; MS226.008.010.00003 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Kelley, Carolyn (2 of 3), 2002; MS226.008.010.00004 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Kelley, Carolyn (3 of 3), 2002; MS226.008.010.00005 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Kelley, Carolyn - depositions, 2001 -- 2003; MS226.008.010.00006 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Key Porter Books, 2010; MS226.008.010.00007 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Klonsky, Ken (1 of 2), 2002 -- 2008; MS226.008.010.00008 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Klonsky, Ken (2 of 2), 2002 -- 2008; MS226.008.010.00009 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Jamaica, 1998 -- 1999; MS226.008.010.00010 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Lakehead University, 1998; MS226.008.010.00011 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Mandela, Nelson, 2005; MS226.008.010.00012 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Marshall, Andy - "Mustard Seed" movie, 2004; MS226.008.010.00013 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Martin, Lesra, 2000; MS226.008.010.00014 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Mayo, William - Georgia, 2003; MS226.008.010.00015 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - McCallum, David (1 of 5), 1986 -- 2010; MS226.008.010.00016 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - McCallum, David (2 of 5), 1986 -- 2010; MS226.008.010.00017 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - McCallum, David (3 of 5), 1986 -- 2010; MS226.008.010.00018 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - McCallum, David (4 of 5), 1986 -- 2010; MS226.008.010.00019 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - McCallum, David (5 of 5), 1986 -- 2010; MS226.008.010.00020 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - McElliott, Patrick, 2001; MS226.008.010.00021 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Metnick, Michael, 2005; MS226.008.010.00022 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Miller, Lawrence, 1996; MS226.008.010.00023 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Mint, Morty - contracts, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.008.010.00024 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Movie clippings, 1998; MS226.008.010.00025 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Mr. Big, 2008; MS226.008.010.00026 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Murnaghan, Michael - court case, 2001 -- 2002; MS226.008.010.00027 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Murnaghan, Michael - disciplinary (chartered account), 2002; MS226.008.010.00028 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Murray, Lynne - Canadian High Commission, Trinidad, 2003; MS226.008.010.00029 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Nguyen Thi Hiep, 2001; MS226.008.010.00030 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 10)
  - Odidi, De Isa, 2004; MS226.008.011.00001 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Ogletree, Charles Jr., 1999; MS226.008.011.00002 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Parsons, Gregory, 2003; MS226.008.011.00003 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Partisan Defense Committee, 1999 -- 2000; MS226.008.011.00004 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Partisan Defense Committee, 2006 -- 2011; MS226.008.011.00005 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Penthouse interview, 1998; MS226.008.011.00006 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Peterborough - Fleming College, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.008.011.00007 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Photographer - Jeff Boal, 2002; MS226.008.011.00008 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Postmortem project, 2001; MS226.008.011.00009 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Press, 2000 -- 2004; MS226.008.011.00010 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Program Corporation of America, 2002; MS226.008.011.00011 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Promos, 1998 -- 2004; MS226.008.011.00012 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Pulec, Boris, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.008.011.00013 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Queen's University - application for LLB and Order of Canada, Nobel Peace Prize, 2003; MS226.008.011.00014 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Rafay, Atif - money for education, 2009; MS226.008.011.00015 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Revenue Canada - budget, 2003; MS226.008.011.00016 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Richmond Free Press, 2000; MS226.008.011.00017 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Sampson, William, 2002; MS226.008.011.00018 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Sarokin, H. Lee, 1992 -- 1999; MS226.008.011.00019 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Savory, Johnnie - petition for clemency, 2003 -- 2004; MS226.008.011.00020 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Slaby, Steve, 1975 -- 1999; MS226.008.011.00021 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Soffar, Max, 2000 -- 2003; MS226.008.011.00022 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Southern Center for Human Rights (1 of 2), 1998 -- 2003; MS226.008.011.00023 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Southern Center for Human Rights (2 of 2), 1998 -- 2003; MS226.008.011.00024 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Southern Center for Human Rights - Stephen Bright, 2003; MS226.008.011.00025 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Speaking engagements - done, 1998 -- 2003; MS226.008.011.00026 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - St. Elizabeth Catholic High School, 2002; MS226.008.011.00027 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Stamps, 1950 -- 1990; MS226.008.011.00028 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Subway Elvis, 2001; MS226.008.011.00029 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Summer Garden Winter Lights, Inc., 2004; MS226.008.011.00030 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - The Sun response, 2003; MS226.008.011.00031 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Terry, Paul - DNA, 2003; MS226.008.011.00032 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Tjapkes, Doug, 2006; MS226.008.011.00033 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Truscott, Steve - Julian Sher, 2001; MS226.008.011.00034 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Trustee of Foundation - Friends of Griffith University, Lisa, 2006; MS226.008.011.00035 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - TV interviews, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.008.011.00036 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - University of Tennessee event, 2000; MS226.008.011.00037 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Volz, Eric, 2006 -- 2007; MS226.008.011.00038 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - The Way Community Center, Swainsboro, Georgia, 1999; MS226.008.011.00039 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Walker, Alan, 2005; MS226.008.011.00040 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Waller, Kevin, 1995 -- 1997; MS226.008.011.00041 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Waller, Kevin - JET Jamaica, 2006; MS226.008.011.00042 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Walsh, Erin, 2009; MS226.008.011.00043 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Watson, Scott - brief, 2004; MS226.008.011.00044 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - The Week That Was - resignation, 2004; MS226.008.011.00045 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Who's Who in Black Canada, 2002; MS226.008.011.00046 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Wheels, 2002; MS226.008.011.00047 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Willoughby, Daniel Hayden - appeal, 2003; MS226.008.011.00048 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Wong, Anthony, 2004; MS226.008.011.00049 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Worn Free, LLC - merchandise license, 2009; MS226.008.011.00050 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Writers' Union of Canada - grievance against Porter Books, 2005 -- 2007; MS226.008.011.00051 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Wrongly Convicted, 2005 -- 2007; MS226.008.011.00052 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - Yellowhead Tribal Council, 2000; MS226.008.011.00053 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - York University, 2005; MS226.008.011.00054 (Box data_value_missing_f2d76c9d224d0fa7189592e1430be61e, Box 11)
  - BBC - Liza radio interview audiocassette, 2001; MS226.008.016.00003 (Box data_value_missing_0528436d08824cc30c17cc57fc820553, Box 16)
    Removed from box 7 for preservation purposes.
- Writings, 1970 -- 2012; MS226.009; 3.6 Linear Feet
  Writings include Carter's notes, speeches, and drafts of articles and books in computer printout, typescript, and manuscript formats. There are also writings by other authors sent to Carter for review. Older material in this series is somewhat tattered and should be used with care.
  Arranged in two subseries: 1. Writings by Carter; 2. Writings by others. Arranged alphabetically within subseries.
  - Writings by Carter, 1970 -- 2012; MS226.009.001; 3.6 Linear Feet
    - Boxing, 1970 -- 1979; MS226.009.001.012.00001 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - The Door in the Wall draft, 1980 -- 1999; MS226.009.001.012.00002 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - The Door in the Wall, draft, 1989; MS226.009.001.012.00003 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Excerpt from Eye of the Hurricane, 2011; MS226.009.001.012.00004 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Eye of the Hurricane, chapters 2 and 3, drafts, 2004 -- 2011; MS226.009.001.012.00005 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Eye of the Hurricane, chapters 1 - 5, drafts, 2005; MS226.009.001.012.00006 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - In Terms of Sex, Whose Kidding Who?, 1970 -- 1989; MS226.009.001.012.00007 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - The Myth About the Sophistication of Racism, 1970 -- 1979; MS226.009.001.012.00008 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - No Holds Barred and No Bars to Hold, partial revised drafts, 1970 -- 1999; MS226.009.001.012.00009 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Notes, 1970 -- 1989; MS226.009.001.012.00010 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Notes and correspondence, 1970 -- 1979; MS226.009.001.012.00011 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Notes and drafts (1 of 2), 1970 -- 1989; MS226.009.001.012.00012 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Notes and drafts (2 of 2), 1970 -- 1989; MS226.009.001.012.00013 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Notes and to-do lists, 2000 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00014 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Pleasure and Freedom, 1970 -- 1989; MS226.009.001.012.00015 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Roast of Carmen Basilio, 1990 -- 2009; MS226.009.001.012.00016 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Salt in Humanity, 1970 -- 1989; MS226.009.001.012.00017 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech, 1980 -- 1999; MS226.009.001.012.00018 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech at ABA conference, 1993; MS226.009.001.012.00019 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech at Bring Leonard Peltier Home, 2012; MS226.009.001.012.00020 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech at Death Penalty Conference, Santa Barbara, 2003; MS226.009.001.012.00021 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech at Fairleigh Dickinson University - Change is Necessary, 1991; MS226.009.001.012.00022 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)
    - Speech at Griffith University, 2003; MS226.009.001.012.00023 (Box data_value_missing_4f0696a6584067640774aa28075aa367, Box 12)